{"data":[{"question":"In 1975, according to the national center for health statistics, the average life expectancy for people born during that year ________ 72.4 years.","a":"is","b":"were","c":"are","d":"was","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Tense agreement: When the main clause is in past tense, in the subordinate clause the past tense shows another completed action related in time to the main action.\u00a0\n- Subject (the average life expectancy) is singular.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"A ________ mountaineer reached the top of the Himalaya last week.","a":"fearful","b":"fearfulness","c":"fearless","d":"fearlessness","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Adj + noun.\u00a0\n- Fearless: not afraid of anything.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"Traditionally, the flag is ________ in the morning and taken down at night.","a":"raised","b":"raise","c":"risen","d":"rise","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Passive voice : to be + pp.\u00a0\n- Raise: It is a fairly formal way to say \"lift something up\" or \"move something up\".","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"One way to inform the public about factories that pollute the environment is through ________ programs on TV.","a":"agricultural","b":"educational","c":"industrial","d":"cultural","answer":"2","explain":"\n- An educational program is often used to inform\/teach people something.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"I didn't enjoy this book on how to succeed in business. It wasn't very ________.","a":"poorly written","b":"well typed","c":"well written","d":"good written","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Adv + verb (write).\u00a0\n- Wasn't : implies negative- poorly written is not correct.\u00a0\n- Well typed: no error typing.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"The corals can be divided into three groups, two of which ________ extinct.","a":"is","b":"are","c":"was","d":"were","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Tense agreement: When the main clause is in simple present tense, if the subordinate clause the which shows an action occurring at the same time will be simple present tense.\u00a0\n- Subject (two of which) is plural.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"Without alphabetical order, dictionaries would be ________ to use.","a":"possibility","b":"possible","c":"impossibility","d":"impossible","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Be impossible to do sth: no way to do sth.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"I was shocked ________ the news of the crashed plane.","a":"about","b":"with","c":"of","d":"at","answer":"4","explain":"\n- To be shocked at.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"Jane Addams had already established full house in Chicago and ________ her work in the women's suffrage movement when she was awarded the Nobel prize for peace.","a":"began","b":"begun","c":"begin","d":"beginning","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Begun: in a series of actions happened in past.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"The extent to which an individual is a product of either heredity or environment ________, but several theories have been proposed.","a":"cannot proved","b":"cannot be proved","c":"cannot prove","d":"can be proved","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Passive voice with modal verb (can\/could\/ will, may...): can\/could\/ will\/may...+ be +PP.\u00a0\n- Negative: can\/could\/ will\/may...+ Not+ be + PP.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"}]}